

## **LUISINA GISELA TORCASSI**

Public accountant with more than five years of experience in external auditing, performing my work in companies within the following areas: oil & gas, financial services and construction. With a solid knowledge in the analysis of financial statements and internal control audit (SOX).

Acquiring new knowledge in computer tools and data analysis to improve the quality of my work.

### **CONTACT**

Phone:+34 695 779 515

Email:luisinatorcassi@hotmail.com

Address: Barcelona, Spain



#### **EDUCATION**

Universidad Empresarial Siglo 21, Buenos Aires, Argentina. March 2020 – June 2023 (Graduate)

Master's in business administration -MBA

Universidad Nacional de La Matanza, Buenos Aires, Argentina. April 2011- June 2017 (Graduate)

**Public Accountant** 

## **EXPERIENCE**

**KPMG** Argentina

July 2021 - July 2022

Job title: Consultant Sr. Internal Audit, Risk & Compliance Services Present

Carrying out internal audits of processes, identification and evaluation of risks, development and optimization of internal administrative, accounting and financial circuits, application and control of internal regulations (SOX regulations, among others), presentation of reports to clients and implementation of best practices internal audit.

#### October 2018- June 2021

Job title: Senior External Auditor

- Internal control audit (SOX): Carry out proper planning and auditing of internal control.

  Beginning with the establishment of the description of the processes of a company, the evaluation of the design of controls and the realization of the walkthroughs of processes.

  Continuing with the selection of key controls, assembly of universes on which the samples submitted to the corresponding testing will be obtained. At the end of testing, it is possible to obtain conclusions related to the operational and design efficiency of the controls, establishing their effectiveness or lack of effectiveness, analyzing the possible potential impact on the different business areas of the company.
- EECC Audit through the preparation of analytical, detailed and control tests. Compilation and review of EECC under local standard, of EEFF under IFRS standard submitted to CNV and EEFF under US GAAP standard. Joint supervision and training of a medium team. Analysis of processes and verification of compliance with the internal control of an entity. Preparation of analytical reviews. EEFF consolidation review. Management of eAudit and IDEA audit systems.

January 2017 – September 2018

Job title: Semi-Senior External Auditor

**December 2016- December 2017**Job title: Junior External Auditor

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Curso análisis de datos Python IEEE-ITBA (Oct. 2023)
- Curso Introductorio de Python IEEE-ITBA (Ago. 2023)
- If programmed: Argentina Program 4.0 –
   INTI (Apr. 2023)
- Preparing for Your Associate Cloud
   Engineer Journey Coursera (Dic. 2022)
- Architecting with Google Compute Engine in Spanish. – Coursera (Nov. 2022)
- Essential Cloud Infrastructure: Core Services – Coursera (Oct. 2022)
- Essential Cloud Insfrastructure: Foundation – Coursera (Oct. 2022)
- Google Cloud Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure – Coursera (Oct. 2022)
- Introducción a MySQL Platzi (Sep. 2022)
- Curso práctico SQL Platzi (Ago. 2022)
- SQL esencial Linkedin (Oct. 2020)
- Diplomatura en Business Intelligence UTN (Ago 2018)

### **APTITUDES**

- COSO framework
- Ley Sarbanes-Oxley
- Database development
- Optimization of processes
- Industry Oil & Gas
- External audit
- EEFF
- Internal audit
- Risk assessment
- Politics and procedures
- Teamwork
- Segregation of functions
- Optimization of processes

# **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish: Native
- English: Professional competency

## **SKILLS**

- Microsoft Office
- Microsoft Power BI
- SAP
- SQL
- Tableau
- Looker
- Google Cloud Platform (GCP)